ZEYNEP ÇIRÇIR

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I'm Zeynep Çırçır, a Computer Engineering student with a focuson frontend development. I specialize in Angular technology, crafting interactive and responsive user interfaces. My skillsinclude HTML, CSS, and TypeScript, enabling me to combinetechnical prowess with creativity. As a software developer intern, I am committed to delivering cutting-edge solutions in the techfield, backed by my fluency in English.

SKILLS

- Eager to learn and implement cutting edge techs
- Good at problem analysis and solving
- Goog at learning new things fast

EDUCATION

KARABUK UNIVERSITY

KARABUK UNIVERSITY

Computer Engineering(%100 English)

Level 4rd | 09/2020-Present

Preparation Education
Level B2 | 09/2019-06/2020

EXPERIENCE

SMARTICT BİLİŞİM A.Ş.

02/2024 - Present | Ankara

Frontend Development Long Term Intern (Angular)

ENOCA™ INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES

11/2023 - 01/2023 | Karabük

I work as a frontend developer intern. I am improving my skills in this fieldby using Angular technology.

EAE TECHNOLOGY

08/2022 - 09/2022 | İstanbul

During the internship, i did work in the field of frontend.

T3 FOUNDATION / TRAINER - MENTOR FOUNDATION

03/2023 - 12/2023,

I work as an trainer and mentor in the Özdemir Bayraktarscholarship program.

VOLUNTEERING

TEKNOFEST SOFTWARE TEAM MEMBER

05/2021 - 02/2022,

I worked in OCTAGON and NATUR-AUV teams. We competed in the Teknofest unmannedunderwater advanced category.

IEEE KBU COMPUTER SOCIETY CHAIRMAN

11/2021 - 09/2023,

I am the chairman of the IEEE CS branch in ourschool.